A Guide to the Records of the Office of the Vice President for Administration, Stuart K. Cassell, 1945-1975
Special Collections and University Archives, Virginia Tech
- 1949
  - Power Plant Addition – Bids for Apparatus & Piping Opened 3/24/49, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - President's Home, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Quarrying Stone, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - R Miscellaneous, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - R. Stuart Royer & Associates, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Radford Project, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Refrigerated Storage Rooms – Horticulture Work, Virginia Agricultural Experiment Station, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - S Miscellaneous, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Saunders, Fred Q. – Chief Engineer, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Student Employees, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Student Life Committee, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Swink, H.W. – Purchasing Agent & Personnel Officer, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - T Miscellaneous, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Trailer Camps, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Tuck, Governor William M., 1949 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - U Miscellaneous, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - United Carbon Company, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - V.P.I. Research Foundation, Inc., 1949 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Veterans Administration, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - W Miscellaneous, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Wiley & Wilson – Consulting Engineers, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Young, H.N. – Director, Agricultural Experiment Station, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- 1950
  - Accounts & Purchases, Division of, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Administrative Council, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Allotments – Advice, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Allotments from Richmond – Quarterly Allotment Estimate, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Alumni Association, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Athletic Association, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Auditor's Report, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Bennett, J. Gordon – State Auditor of Public Accounts, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Bradford, J.H. – Director of the Budget, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Budget Matters – 1950-52 Biennium, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Capital Outlay Items – Approved, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Chas. Lunsford Sons and Izard Insurance, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Cregger, S.G. – Auditor, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Cregger & Dekker – Joint Letters, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Dekker, H.J. – Treasurer, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Federal Power Commission, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - First and Merchants National Bank – Release of Bonds and Notes Held in Escrow, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Gathright, A.B. – Director, Division of Purchase & Printing, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - "Highlands", 1950 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Hutcheson, J.R. – Chancellor, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - J Miscellaneous, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Landscaping – A.A. Farnham, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Mall, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Meat Animal & Poultry Processing Laboratory Project (4 folders), 1950 (Box 7, Folder 34-37)
  - Poultry Plant (3 folders), 1950 (Box 7, Folder 38-40)
  - Power Plant, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - S Miscellaneous, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Student Aid Association, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Trailer Camps, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - V.P.I. Research Foundation, Inc., 1950 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Veterans Administration, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 46)
- 1951
  - Allotments from Richmond – Quarterly Allotment Estimate, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Bradford, J.H. – Director of the Budget, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Capital Outlay Items – Approved, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Carneal & Johnston, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Chas. Lunsford Sons and Izard Insurance, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Closing Time of Buildings, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - College Statements – Experiment Station Extension Division (2 folders), 1951 (Box 8, Folder 7-8)
  - Cregger, S.G. – Auditor, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Cregger & Dekker – Joint Letters, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Engineering Laboratory (4 folders), 1951 (Box 8, Folder 11-14)
  - Extending of Heat Lines and Additional Connections to Steam Lines, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Farm Shop & Implement Building – Eastern Virginia Field Station, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Federal Power Commission, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Fire Damage in World War I Memorial, 1951-08-30 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - I Miscellaneous, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Personnel, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - State Fire Marshal's Report, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Study Conducted by Mr. James – State Auditor's Office, 1951-06-06 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Tidewater Field Station, Holland, VA – Main Office and Laboratory Building, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - V.P.I. Research Foundation, Inc., 1951 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Word, T.S. – Attorney, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- 1952
  - Abbitt, J.R. – Director, Buildings and Grounds, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Accounts and Purchases, Division of, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Administrative Council, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Allotments from Richmond – Quarterly Allotment Estimate, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Architects Applying for Library Designing Project, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - B Miscellaneous, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Blanket Letters, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Boone, James F. – Treasurer, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Bradford, J.H. – Director of the Budget, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Buck, Dr. J.L. Blair – Coordinator of Teacher Education, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - C Miscellaneous, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Capital Outlay Items – Approved, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Carneal & Johnston, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Chas. Lunsford Sons and Izard Insurance, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Cregger, S.G. – Auditor, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - D Miscellaneous, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Duties of Auditor & Treasurer, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Faculty Center – List of Furniture, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Federal Power Commission, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Fire Marshall Reports, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Greenhouse at Holland, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - H Miscellaneous, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Hay Drying and Storage Shed, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - I.B.M. Information, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - L Miscellaneous, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Livestock & Poultry Disease Research Laboratory, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - M Miscellaneous, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Military Affairs, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Monthly Statement of Revenues Other Than From Appropriations, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - N Miscellaneous, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - [Folder removed from collection] (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Personnel, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - President's Special Committee, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Purchase of Robert Richardson Farm, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - S Miscellaneous, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Social Security Program, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Station WUVT in S.A.B., 1952 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Student Life Committee, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Swink, H.W. – Purchasing Agent & Personnel Officer, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Traffic Regulations, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Trailers, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Vandenberg, H.P.C. – Planning Engineer, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Veteran's Administration, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - "Whitethorne" Land from Mr. Heth, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Young, H.N. – Director, Virginia Agricultural Experiment Station, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- 1953
  - Abbitt, J.R. – Director, Buildings & Grounds, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Advisory Legislative Council, VA, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Allotments from Richmond – Quarterly Allotment Estimate, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - B Miscellaneous, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Blanket Letters, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Boone, James F. – Treasurer, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Bradford, J.H. – Director of the Budget, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Buck, Dr. J.L. Blair – Coordinator of Teacher Education, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - C Miscellaneous, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - D Miscellaneous, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Daughtery, W.H. – Director of Extension Service, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - DeBusk, C.F. – Utility Engineer, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Devine, General John M. – Commandant of Cadets, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Dietrick, L.B. – Dean of Agriculture, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Disease Research Laboratory – Livestock & Poultry (2 folders), 1953 (Box 9, Folder 31-32)
  - Experimental Tobacco Barns at the Southwest Virginia Research Station, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Federal Power Commission, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - G Miscellaneous, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Legislature, Visit of, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Litton, George W. – Head, Animal Husbandry Department, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - M Miscellaneous, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Middleburg – Bids on Northern Virginia Experiment Station Timber, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Minter, S.R. – Manager, V.P.I. Electric Service, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Monthly Statement of Revenues Other Than From Appropriations, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Newman, Walter S. – President, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Personal, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Personnel, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Speeches, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Swink, H.W. – Purchasing Agent & Personnel Officer, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Vandenberg, H.P.C. – Planning Engineer, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Water Works, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Whittemore, J.W. – Dean of Engineering, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Word, T.S. – Attorney, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Young, H.N. – Director, Virginia Agricultural Experiment Station, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 51)
- 1954
  - A Miscellaneous, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Accounts and Purchases, Division of, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Allotments from Richmond, Quarterly Allotment Estimates, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Athletic Association, V.P.I., 1954 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Athletic Field Development, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Auditor's Reports, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - B Miscellaneous, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Blanket Letters, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Boone, J.F. – Treasurer, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Bradford, J.H. – Director of the Budget, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - C Miscellaneous, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - Coal Analysis, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Commission on State Capital Outlay, C.H. Morrissett, Chairman, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Cregger, S.G. – Auditor, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - DeBusk, C.F. – Utility Engineer, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - Dietrick, L.B. – Dean of Agriculture, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - Electric Control Panels, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - Electric Control Panels (Switchgear) (2 folders), 1954 (Box 9, Folder 69-70)
  - J Miscellaneous, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 71)
  - K Miscellaneous, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 72)
  - Newman, Walter S. – President, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 73)
  - Pardue, Louis A. – Vice President, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 74)
  - Personal, S.K. Cassell, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - Questionnaires, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 76)
  - Research Corporation, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 77)
  - Sowder, Allen – Attorney, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 78)
  - Stanley, Honorable Thomas B. – Governor of Virginia, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 79)
  - Swink, H.W. – Purchasing Agent & Personnel Officer, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 80)
  - Tate, Dr. Mildred – Head, Home Economics Department, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 81)
  - W Miscellaneous, Water Authority, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 82)
  - Whittemore, J.W. – Dean of Engineering, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 83)
- 1955
  - Advisory Legislative Council, Virginia, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Agronomy Department-Dr. H.L Dunton and others, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Allotment Record, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Allotments from Richmond, Quarterly Allotment Estimates, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Alumni Association, V.P.I, -H.B. Redd, Secretary, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts-J. Gordon Bennett and others (2 folders), 1955 (Box 10, Folder 6-7)
  - Auditor's Reports, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - B-Miscellaneous, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Boone, J.F.- Treasurer, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Bradford, J.H.- Director of Budget, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Capital Outlay, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Cattle Barns (2 folders), 1955 (Box 10, Folder 13-14)
  - Commerce Building, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Comparison of Appropriations by Divisions-Land Grant Colleges, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Cregger, S.G.-Auditor, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - DeBusk, C.F.- Utility Engineer, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Farm Tenant Houses, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Federal Power Commission, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Golf Course, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - King, Howard P.- Director of Dining Halls, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Personal Office Reorganization Study, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - S-Miscellaneous, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Television, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Whittmore, John W., Dean of Engineering, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Young, Dr. H.N.-Director Agriculture Engineering Station, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- 1956
  - Abbott, Stanley W.- Landscape Architecture, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Admission-Statistics, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Auditor's Reports, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Boone, J.F. Treasurer, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Bradford, J.H.-Director of Budget, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Cregger, S.G, Auditor, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Daughtrey, W.H. Associate Director of Agricultural Extension Service, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - DeBusk, C.F.- Utility Engineer, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Dietrick, L.B. Dean of Agriculture, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Evans, E.B.-Personal Officer, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Federal Power Commission, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Fire Damage- Davidson Hall, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Highways-State Department, 1955-1956 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - National Science Foundation, 1955-1956 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Newman, Walter S.-President, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Personal- State Office, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - R-Miscellaneous, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Sowder, Allan- Attorney, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Stanley, Honorable Thomas B.- Governor, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Traffic Committee, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Young, Dr. H.N.-Director Agriculture Engineering Station, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 48)
- 1957
  - Abbitt, J.R., Director- Department of Buildings and Grounds, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Advisory Legislative Council, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Annexation, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Attorney General's Decisions-Miscellaneous (2 folders), 1957 (Box 10, Folder 52-53)
  - Bennett, J. Gordon-Auditor of Public Accounts, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Bradford, J.H.-Director of Budget, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Chamber of Commerce, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Committee on Accounting Procedures, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Committee Salary Adjustment, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Day, Sidney C.-State Comptroller, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - DeBusk, C.F.- Utility Engineer, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Dietrick, L.G. Dean of Agriculture, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Evans, E.B.-Personnel Officer, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - Farrier, Dr. Paul H. –Executive Secretary, State Council of Higher Education, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Federal Power Commission, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - Land Condemnation, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - M-Miscellaneous, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - McBryde Property, 1935-1957 (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - National Science Foundation, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - Personnel State Office, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 69)
  - Questionnaires, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 70)
  - Water Treatment for Power Plant Boilers, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 71)
  - Whittmore, J.W. Dean of Engineering, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 72)
  - Young, Dr. H.N.-Director Agriculture Experiment Station, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 73)
- 1958
  - Audio-Visual Program, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Agronomy Department, H.L Dunton-Head, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- 1959
  - Allotments from Richmond-Quarterly Allotments Estimates, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Almond, Honorable J. Lindsay-Governor, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Auditor's Reports, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - B-Miscellaneous, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Boone, J.F.-Treasurer, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Contracts-Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Contractors-Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Cregger,, S.G.-Auditor, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Day, Sidney C.-State Comptroller, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - DeBusk, C.F.- Utility Engineer, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Development Program (2 folders), 1959 (Box 11, Folder 14-15)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare Department of, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Higher Education, State Council of, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Krug, Dr. R.C.-Head of Chemistry Department, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Kuhn, L.M.-Director of Budget, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Nuclear Insurance, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Personnel-State Office, John W. Garber and others, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Purchase and Printing, State Department of, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Sowder, Allen-Attorney, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - VPI Athletic Association- F.O. Moseley, Director, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Young, Dr. H.N.-Director Agricultural Experiment, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- 1960
  - Attorney General's Decisions-Carry Over from year to year, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Attorney General's Decisions- Students, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Sieburth- Phaeocysth, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Federal Loan Program-Brought Forward (3 folders), 1960 (Box 16, Folder 1-3)
- 1961
  - Agriculture Experiment Station- Dr. H.M. Young and others, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Agriculture Expansion Service-W.H. Daughtrey, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Agronomy Department- H.L. Dunton,Head, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Allotment Information-Operating, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Allotments from Richmond-Quarterly Allotment Estimates, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Alumni Association-Marcus Oliver, Secretary, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Atomic Energy Commission-Division of Licensing and Registration, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Auditor's Report, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - B-Miscellaneous, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Budget Information, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Capital Outlays- (2 folders), 1961-06-30-1962-07-01 (Box 11, Folder 39-40)
  - Central Storeroom Project, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Chemistry Department-R.C. Krug-Head, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Contractor's Correspondence-Miscellaneous, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Debusk, C.F.- Heat and Power, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Extension Schools-Danville, Norfolk, Roanoke, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Governor J. Lindsay Almond, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Highways, State Department of, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, Department of, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - King, Howard P. Jr.-Director of Food Service, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - L-Miscellaneous, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Southwest Virginia Tobacco Barn, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Turkey Research Plant-Second Phase, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Agricultural Conference Board, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- 1962
  - Capital Outlays- (2 folders), 1962-07-30-1963-07-01 (Box 12, Folder 2 to 12-3)
  - Closing Times of Campus Buildings Committee, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Community Colleges, Clifton Forge and Covington (2 folders), 1962 (Box 12, Folder 5-6)
  - Community Colleges, Galax, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Debusk, C.F.- Heat and Power, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Fundraising and Development, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Governor's Allotment Authorizations for the 1962-64 Biennium, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Inauguration of Dr. Hahn, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Lease of Stone Quarry- Hassel H. Price and others, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - NASA Langely Field Wind Tunnel, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - NASA Space Radiations Effects Laboratory, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Oakland Estates Inc, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Roanoke Technical Institute, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - State Council on Higher Education, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - State Director of the Budget- L.M. Kuhn, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - State Division of Statutory Research and Drafting, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - State Treasury Department, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - State Water Control Board, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Statement of Revenue other than from Appropriations Monthly, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Student Affairs, Dr. James W. Dean, Director, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Student Aid Association- H.H. McEver, Secretary, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Tailor Shop, W.W. Dobyns, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Town of Blacksburg, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Vandenberg, H.P.C, Planning Engineer, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - WXYZ Miscellaneous, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Cost Study Committee-State Institutions of Higher Learning (2 folders), 1962 (Box 15, Folder 25-26)
- 1963
  - Academic Council (3 folders), 1963 (Box 12, Folder 29-31)
  - Admissions- Dr. Paul Farrier, Director, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station- Dr. H.N. Young, Director, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Agricultural Extension Service, Mr. W.H. Daughtrey, Director, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Agronomy Department- Dr. H.L. Dunton, Head, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Airport, Mr. T.F. Broce, Manager, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Allotments from Richmond- Quarterly Allotments Estimates, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Alumni Association- Marcus Oliver-Secretary, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Animal Husbandry Department- Mr. George Litton-Head, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Architecture Department, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Athletic Association- Mr. F.O. Moseley, Director, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Attorney General, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Auditor's Report, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - B-Miscellaneous, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Bank Correspondence, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Bell, Dean Wilson B.- School of Agriculture, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Biochemistry and Nutrition Department, Dr. R.L Engel, Head, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Biology Department- Dr. F.S. Orcutt, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Blanket Letters, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Boone, J.F.- Treasurer, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Brandt, Dr. Warren W.- Vice President, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Budget Material, 1962-1963 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - C-Miscellaneous, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Capital Outlays- (2 folders), 1963-07-01-1964-06-30 (Box 12, Folder 54-55)
  - Cassell, Stuart K- Personal, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Cato, W.H.- Director, Guidance and Placement, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Chas. Lunsford Sons and Izard Insurance, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Chemistry Department- Dr. R.C. Krug, Head, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Committee-Alumni Homecoming, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Committee-Commencement, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Committee-Community Development-Governor's, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Community College, Danville, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Community College-Old Dominion College, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Community College- Roanoke Technical Institute, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Contract Correspondence-Miscellaneous, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Cooperative Program- H. Stuart Smith, Director, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - D-Miscellaneous, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Dairy Science Department. Dr. G.C. Graf, Head, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Debusk, C.F.- Heat and Power, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - F-Miscellaneous, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - E-Miscellaneous, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Engineering Experiment Station-J.R. Lucas-Acting Director, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Evans, E.B.-Director of Personnel, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - F-Miscellaneous, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Fabian, Craig- Director of Development and Public Relations, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Fireworks on Campus, Display of, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 22)